<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overview on Camunda 8 Training</title>
    <link>/c8/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overview on Camunda 8 Training</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/c8/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1 Designing a process</title>
      <link>/c8/1-designing-a-process-in-web-modeler/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/c8/1-designing-a-process-in-web-modeler/</guid>
      <description>Background In this exercise you are asked to design a process using BPMN and DMN. The scenario description can be found in the next section. To model it use the Camunda 8 Web Modeler https://modeler.cloud.camunda.io/.
Task: Model the following process. We are designing a process to manage the quarantine of persons infected with HZV - the &amp;ldquo;Hypothetical Zombie Virus&amp;rdquo;. Statistically, 5% of people who are infected with the Zombie Virus turn into actual undead Zombies, with an insatiable craving to eat human brains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Getting familiar with C8</title>
      <link>/c8/2-getting-familiar-with-camunda-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/c8/2-getting-familiar-with-camunda-8/</guid>
      <description>Background After having modelled and aligned on our process diagram we are now going to discover the capabilities of Camunda 8.
Task: Try out Camunda 8 features Camunda Platform 8 is powered by Zeebe, a new class of BPMN workflow engine that delivers true horizontal scalability and enables high-performance use cases that were once beyond the realm of workflow automation.
The Camunda 8 Console https://console.cloud.camunda.io/ acts as an entry point to Camunda Platform 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Adding User Tasks and Forms</title>
      <link>/c8/3-adding-user-tasks-and-forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/c8/3-adding-user-tasks-and-forms/</guid>
      <description>Background We have created a process in our Camunda Platform 8 environment during exercise 1 already. In this section we want to deploy this process after having added Camunda Forms to a User Task.
Task: Add User Tasks and a Form to the User Tasks In the animated image below - showing a single user task - you can see how to change the type of activity. After having done so we can change some User Task specific properties such as the assignee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Automating the process</title>
      <link>/c8/4-automating-the-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/c8/4-automating-the-process/</guid>
      <description>Background Now, we are ready to automate the process we have created and aligned on. Below you can find a representation of that process.
Task: Automate the process To automate this process three steps need to be automated:
Notify the person to quarantine Generate certificate of recovery Send certificate of recovery Automation in Camunda Platform is implemented using the external worker pattern. &amp;ldquo;Glue code&amp;rdquo; is code that you write in a worker to glue the automation to external services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Analysing the process</title>
      <link>/c8/5-analysing-the-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/c8/5-analysing-the-process/</guid>
      <description>Background Having automated the process and tried it out multiple times, we are ready to analyse the process in Optimize.
Task: Use Optimize to analyze the process This tool helps you to create business-friendly reports and dashboards as well as alerts that help you to identify process bottlenecks and improve the overall performance of your end-to-end process.
To get started, please launch the Optimize application from your Cluster and create a new collection for our reports and dashboards.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
